//Initialize JSON object
var about = {
	"info": [
	{
		"question": "What is your name?",
		"answer": "Levi Hand"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is your chat user name, including the host?",
		"answer": "On AIM, it's lhand1986@yahoo.com"
	},
	{
		"question": "In which time zone do you reside?",
		"answer": "Pacific"
	},
	{
		"question": "Why are you in the Mobile Development program?",
		"answer": "I've always wanted to program for different technologies."
	},
	{
		"question": "How comfortable are you with Javascript?",
		"answer": "Relatively comfortable with what we have learned so far."
	},
	{
		"question": "How comfortable are you with Titanium?",
		"answer": "Also relatively comfortable. This program should be a good refresher."
	},
	{
		"question": "What is your favorite TV show?",
		"answer": "Doctor Who"
	},
	{
		"question": "Who is your favorite author?",
		"answer": "Robert Jordan"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is your favorite book?",
		"answer": "The Eye of the World"
	},
	{
		"question": "What kind of work do you do?",
		"answer": "I work in the labor department of a steel mill."
	},
	{
		"question": "What is your favorite sport?",
		"answer": "Dancesport"
	}
	]
};
exports.aboutCall = about;